You tell the authority for these days and time.
I'm too as adication by pastor of my own friend's church day
with Fraser.
I don't see David.
So, Phil, do you want to pinch it?
Yeah.
I could do that.
I didn't think I was first to bring him
about attention to number 15.
Yeah.
No.
No, in all seriousness, let's ask Lord of this with prayer.
Father, we thank you tonight for the city we live in.
We thank you to the leaders.
We thank you for all those that are the civil servants in our community.
Thank you.
A lot more for just the safety that you provide your citizens and the recent tornado.
We ask you to continue protection upon them as the storms are all through North East Oklahoma again.
Father, ask you to just give the council wisdom to do your business and we ask this all in Jesus name.
Amen.
Thank you.
I'd like to leave this to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation and a God into this world with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Thank you, Phil.
I'm poor is public input.
None of this casual personal appearances.
Anyone who wants to address the authority on any of the agenda items.
I'm not already planning to speak.
Item five is a concern agenda and which consists of item six seven and eight claims minutes in some budget amendments.
If there are no questions on any of those items, they're trying to emotion to approve the consent agenda as recommended.
Looks to prove.
And a second please.
Second, roll call.
What's there?
Louis, hi, forget.
All right.
Item nine is accept a reject utility agreement with jam farmers pending approval of annexation.
And in the city of Miami by the city council and that has tired.
Yes, sir.
So this is the first of large agreement that we'll eventually bring for Jane and Farms for us to serve.
You know, then more soon electric.
We will be annexing them in on this city council site.
This is just an agreement with him that we will serve them electricity.
So, you know, as a part of us to being able to serve them electricity is to annex them in.
So that's why we bring that before you on the city council side.
So this is a agreement between the city and jam farms us agreeing to provide electricity.
But it's currently is contingent on approval.
Yes, which we anticipate.
Yes, a problem.
But it is contingent on.
Yes, sir.
Any questions?
Sir, by chance to look at that.
I know if this has been the topic of conversation periodically for the last six months.
If there are no questions, you're concerned.
I'm going to take a motion to approve of item nine, to the motion to accept the utility agreement with Jamfolkens.
Any other second please?
Second.
Go call.
Okay.
All right.
Lewis, I request him.
Hi.
Adam Tanner's other new business and a new business anyone.
Adam 11 is trustee community announcements and the announcements.
Adam 12 was adjourned.
Do we have a motion to adjourn the issue?
Second, that will call please.
Thank you.
All right.
Lewis, hi.